But your television network, I know these guys.
They're from my neck of the woods.
Thank you for your video series.
But your television network, I know these guys.
但是您的电视网络，我知道这些家伙。
Thank you for your video series.
谢谢您的视频系列。
Oh yeah!
哦，是的！
Thanks for watching.
感谢您的观看。
There's the man.
有男人。
Hey, how are you?
嘿，你怎么样？
Look at your setup here.
在这里查看您的设置。
here.
这里。
I'm assembling it. I'm assembling it as we're...
我正在组装。我正在组装...
We are. So good. Well, I'm shooting a long
我们是。超好的。好吧，我正在拍摄很长时间
in a long video. I'll come back around and we'll do a little talk.
在一个长视频中。我会回来，我们会做一些聊天。
We'll talk you bit. You want to do that later? All right, man.
我们会和你说一点。您想稍后再这样做吗？好的，伙计。
everybody
大家
Everybody's from Arrow.
每个人都来自箭。
And then next to them, set dogs. Oh, excuse me.
然后在他们旁边，戴上狗。哦，对不起。
Sad dogs, I don't think this is your last year.
悲伤的狗，我不认为这是你的最后一年。
And then we got the awesome
然后我们得到了很棒的
Awesome and set area.
很棒的设定区域。
Now that takes you into the main room.
现在，这带您进入主房间。
room. The main room is where you got the accent hearing and DX and
房间。主房间是您获得重音听证会和DX的地方
And DX Engineering has vastly, vastly.
DX工程的发展范围很大。
vastly, vastly. How you doing?
大量，大量。你好吗？
Good, good.
好，很好。
eu so
vastly improved their space.
我只是
has gone up like a ton.
像一吨一样上升了。
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
I got some new ones I think.
我想到了一些新的。
and
和
in the video. She got my QSL card not long ago.
在视频中。她不久前就得到了我的QSL卡。
I'm going to go out with a great point of contact in your head.
我将在您的脑海中出去一个很好的联系点。
had their Trevor Bridge. Oh yeah I think so.
有他们的特雷弗桥。哦，是的，我想。
So thank you buddy, appreciate it. I will get you one
所以谢谢哥们，感谢它。我会给你一个
you won back eventually.
您最终赢了。
Appreciate you, but now they got this cool
感谢您，但现在他们变得很酷
That is cool off road vehicle that we're gonna talk to the guys.
那是我们要和这些家伙交谈的很酷的越野车。
the guys that are running this in a second. How you doing?
那些在一秒钟内运行的人。你好吗？
How you doing? Good, good.
你好吗？好，很好。
But before we do that, modern more
但是在我们这样做之前，更多的现代
and he
Remember the modern Morse guys?
还有他
还记得现代摩尔斯的家伙吗？
Where'd he go? Where's our movie?
他去哪里？我们的电影在哪里？
Where's our modern morgue guy? OK.
我们的现代太平间家伙在哪里？好的。
Okay.
好的。
How's it going?
怎么样了？
So we're taking a little look at
所以我们要看一点
I think it's Aaron's keys here.
我认为这是亚伦的钥匙。
He made something.
他做了什么。
then that I came to pick up. I don't know if you.
那我来了。我不知道你是否。
I don't know if he's got it ready for me. If he doesn't, we'll come back. But...
我不知道他是否为我做好了准备。如果他不这样做，我们会回来的。但...
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, you don't have to, I can come.
哦，你不必，我可以来。
I can come back. You just want to say hi and show the key. Yeah.
我可以回来。您只想打个招呼并显示钥匙。是的。
Yeah, just to mention what you're all about.
是的，只是提及您的全部内容。
Just like Bob Barker get it all up in there. Oh right up here
就像鲍勃·巴克（Bob Barker）把所有的东西都放在那里一样。哦，在这里
right up here. Right up here. So yeah, what do you do, man?
就在这里。就在这里。是的，你怎么办？
and if you grab it and show everybody. Oh yeah, sure.
如果您抓住它并向所有人展示。哦，是的，当然。
Thank you.
谢谢。
So, vacation here.
You contacted me a little bit ago and you wanted a key and I said you want
所以，在这里度假。
and I said do you want something engraved? I did. I'm out.
You contacted me a little bit ago and you wanted a key and I said you want
您几点前与我联系，您想要一个钥匙，我说你想要
and I said do you want something engraved? I did. I'm out.
我说你想要刻的东西吗？我做到了。我外出。
And I'm at negative 3db now. You're in there. Okay, cool.
我现在处于负3db。你在那里。好吧，很酷。
Okay, cool, I'm in the pocket. You're in the pocket. You're in the pocket.
好吧，很酷，我在口袋里。你在口袋里。你在口袋里。
That's awesome. Perfect. So, I'm
太棒了。完美的。所以，我
I'm still putting the magnets in these because we just got the magnet shipment in.
我仍在将磁铁放入其中，因为我们刚刚装运了磁铁。
shipment in. But we uh...
运送。但是我们...
Made that key for you there. There's one magnet
在那里为您制作了该钥匙。有一个磁铁
one magnet that needs to still get put on. So.
一个仍需要戴上的磁铁。所以。
So yeah, it's all built, CNC machine.
是的，这都是CNC机器的建造。
We make it in St. Louis at my little machine shop.
我们在我的小机械车间在圣路易斯做到这一点。
shop. I'm like St. Louis, Missouri. Yeah.
店铺。我就像密苏里州圣路易斯。是的。
Yeah. Look at that. That was great.
是的。看看那个。那很棒。
And I have an accessory for you with your other request.
我为您提供其他请求的配件。
requested thing engraved on it but it's not
要求刻有东西，但不是
It's not finished. I'll ship that to you. OK, I know what you're talking about.
还没有完成。我会把那件运送给你。好的，我知道你在说什么。
I know what you're talking about. Let's see, but where's the loophole that we could do it?
我知道你在说什么。让我们看看，但是我们可以做到的漏洞在哪里呢？
do it. So yeah. Yeah. I love it. Yeah. I like it.
做到。是的。是的。我喜欢它。是的。我喜欢它。
I like it. I like it. Okay, right on man. Yeah, I'll come back.
我喜欢它。我喜欢它。好吧，对男人。是的，我会回来的。
come back around and take the key. Take your time. You're going to be busy.
回来拿钥匙。慢慢来。你会很忙。
You only have 100 keys here this weekend.
这个周末您在这里只有100个钥匙。
weekend so yeah you're gonna move through those and we're knocking
周末，是的，您要浏览这些，我们正在敲门
not gonna actually start selling them to all about noon. So, cause I have about
实际上不会在中午开始将它们出售给所有人。所以，因为我有
I have about 40 pre-ordered. The people are like,
我有大约40个预订。人们就像
like showing up just to pick up. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So then at noon, we'll
喜欢出现只是为了捡起。是的，是的。所以中午，我们
and then we'll start selling the other ones. Makes sense. I don't want to make sure I don't accidentally...
然后，我们将开始销售其他销售。有意义。我不想确保我不会意外...
I don't accidentally sell one that somebody says to come pick up. Of course, yeah.
我不会意外地卖一个有人说要接的人。当然，是的。
Yeah, so great on man. Cool. Appreciate you. Thank you.
是的，对男人真好。凉爽的。感谢你。谢谢。
Thanks.
谢谢。
The oil is here.
油在这里。
I just saw on we're gonna
我刚刚看到我们要
We're gonna we're gonna circle around and say what's up. Excuse me.
我们要四处逛逛，说出了什么。打扰一下。
with this cool gladiator look at this thing
有了这个很酷的角斗士看这个东西